Rehn Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  - Walker, Edith - Warner, Keith, 1919-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 799-905)
    Wallace, A. B.
    Wallace, Mrs. G. S.
    Wallace, Josephine
    Wallace, McClelland
    Wallenstein, Alfred
    Waller, B. G.
    Wallingford, Gertrude
    Wallingford, Katrina
    Walsh, Henry
    Walsh, John R.
    Walsh, W.
    Walter, Mrs. W. G.
    Walters, Emile
    Walther League Messenger
    Walton, Joseph E.
    Wands, Alfred
    Warburg, Mrs. Gerald
    Warburg, James P.
    Warner, George B.
    Warner, George C.
    Warner, H. L.
    Warner, Keith
  - Warner, Ruth, 1939-1962 (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 906-998)
  - Warrell - Watherston, 1927-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 999-1031)
    Warrell, Richard
    Warren, Mrs. H. E.
    Warren, Whitney
    Washburn, Mrs. Gordon
    Washburn, Ives
    Washington County Museum of Fine Arts
    Washington Irving Gallery
    Washington University
    Wasserman, Burt
    Wasson, Mrs. William A.
    Watercolor Gallery
    Waters, Sylvia
    Watherston, Margaret M.
  - Watkins, Franklin C. and Ida, 1939-1968, (3 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 1032-1243)
  - Watkins, P. - Winefried, 1918-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 1244-1553)
    Watkins, Franklin C. and Ida
    Watkins, Paul
    Watson, Forbes and Nan
    Watson, Penn R., Jr.
    Watt, S. W.
    Waugh, Colton
    Waugh, Grace W.
    Webb, E. T.
    Webber, Eloise
    Webber, John C.
    Weber, Bill, Jr.
    Weber, E. A.
    Weber, Mosley
    Weber, Mrs. Orlando
    Webster, Hutton, Jr.
    Wechsler, Mrs. Walter M.
    Weed, Bertha A.
    Weeks, Carl
    Weidner, Roswell
    Weinberger, Harry
    Weingarten, Victor
    Weir, Ella Baker (Mrs. J. Alden)
    Weiss, Belle
    Weiss, George
    Weiss, Winefride J.
  - Weid - E. Weyhe Gallery, 1927-1966, undated (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 12-95)
    Weid, F. M.
    Welles, Orson
    Wellesley College
    Wellington, Gertrude
    Wells, Charles E.
    Wells College
    Wells, Fred N.
    Wending, Erwin
    Wengler, Harold
    Wenner, Robert B.
    Anna L. Werbe Galleries
    Wesleyan University, Davison Art Center
    West Valley Tea Room
    Western Association of Art Museum Directors
    Westheimer, Jerome
    Westminster Hotel
    Westover School
    Wetsman, Janis B.
    Wexler, George
    E. Weyhe Gallery
  - WGBH Television - Whitney, Mrs. John Hay, 1919-1967, undated (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 96-157)
    WGBH Television
    Wheaton College
    Wheeler, Charles V.
    Wheeler, Steve
    Wheelwright, Robert
    Whelan, Gloria
    Whimpfheimer, Charles A.
    Whitcomb, John M.
    White, Mr.
    White, A. M.
    White and Quinn
    White, F.
    White, Helen
    White, Jane
    White, John F.
    L. F. White Co.
    White, Marion
    White, Meade Fitzhugh, II
    White, Paul
    White, Mrs. Robert H.
    William A. White and Sons
    Whitehead, Jane Byrd Radcliffe
    Whitehead Productions
    Whitehead, Robert
    Whiteley, James Gustavus
    Whitney, Arthur
    Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt
    Whitney, Mrs. John Hay
  - Whitney Museum of American Art (includes Friends of the Whitney Museum of American Art), 1939-1968, (4 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 158-603)
  - Whitney Studio Club - Wills, 1919-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 604-701)
    Whitney Studio Club
    Whittier, Ross
    Whittington, Eugene
    Wichita Art Association
    Wick, Philip
    Wiegand, Gustav
    Wierke, Conrad
    Wisenberg, Mrs. Louis
    Wiggins, Guy C.
    Wigglesworth, Frank
    Wildenstein and Co., Inc.
    Wilder, Ruth
    Wilk, Mrs. Max
    Wilkinson, Edward A.
    Williams, Charles F.
    Williams College, Lawrence Art Museum
    Williams, E. A.
    Williams, Edgar
    Williams, H. A.
    Williams, Hiram
    Williams, Mrs. Lawrence A.
    Williams, Oliver
    Williams, Wayne F.
    Williard, Robert P.
    Willimantic State College
    Willis, Betty
    Willis, Mrs. Frederic A.
    Wills, Mrs. W. G.
  - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts - Winnipeg Art Gallery Association, 1926-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 702-749)
    Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts
    Wilson Auto Repair Shop
    Wilson, Edwin Carleton
    Wilson, Ralph L.
    Wing, Barbara D.
    Wing, James G.
    Wingate, Arline
    Winnipeg Art Gallery Association
  - Winters, Denny, 1947-1967, (3 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 750-1034)
  - Winters, Helen C. - Woodstock Artists Association, 1920-1967, undated (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1036-1125)
    Winters, Helen C.
    Winton, Flora and Frank J.
    Wise, Howard E.
    Wislocki, George B.
    Witherspoon, Mary Eleanor
    Witte, Edward H., Jr.
    Witte Memorial Museum/San Antonio Art League
    Witter, Faith A.
    Wolf, Ben and Ruth
    Wolf, Stanley J.
    Wolfe, William D.
    Wolfert, Helen
    Wolpin, Kay
    Woman's Day Magazine
    Woman's Home Companion
    Women's American ORT
    Women's Club
    Wood, Franklin S.
    Wood, Charles Erskine Scott
    Wood, Robert W., Jr.
    Ruby Ross Wood, Inc.
    Woodhouse, Betty Burroughs (See also Burroughs, Betty)
    Woodin, Mrs. William H.
    Woodmere Art Gallery
    Woodruff, Adele G.
    Woodstock Artists Association
  - Woodward - Wootton, 1922-1956, undated (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1126-1183)
    Woodward, George
    Woodward, Ruth M.
    Wootton, Ruby Smith
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1924-1959, undated (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1184-1294)
  - Workman - Wylie, 1919-1968, undated (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1295-1414)
    Workman, David T.
    World
    World Book Encyclopedia
    World Collectors Annuary
    World Journal Tribune, Inc.
    Worldwide Press, Inc.
    Worringer, Anne
    Worth Avenue Gallery
    Wose, Frederick
    Wray, Mrs. George D., Jr.
    Wrenn, Helen B. (mother of Peggy W. Rehn)
    Wrenn, Mr. and Mrs. Harold H.
    WRFM Radio
    Wright, Clifford
    Wright, H. P.
    Wright, Norman Bartlett
    Wulp, John
    Wyer's Refrigeration
    Wyeth, Andrew
    Wyeth, John C.
    Wylie, Adele M.
  - Yaddo - Yunt Art Galleries, 1919-1967, undated (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1416-1517)
    Yaddo
    Yale University
    Yale University Art Gallery
    Yamet Arts, Inc.
    Yancey, S. foster
    Yandik, Charles
    Yasinow, J. B.
    Year
    YMCA/YWCA, Ashtabula, Ohio
    YWCA, Fredericksburg, Va.
    YMHA/YWHA, Essex Co., N.J.
    Yocom, Mrs. P.C.
    Yonkers Museum of Science and Arts
    Yorke, Oswald
    Young, E. C.
    Young, Elaine
    Howard Young Galleries
    Young, J. W.
    Young, Katherine
    Young, Mahonri
    Young Stark
    Young, Susan F.
    Young, Mrs. Thomas F.
    Young, William
    Younger, Helen Walcott
    Youngman, William H.
    Youth Today
    Yunt Art Galleries
  - Zabriskie Gallery - Zsissly, 1939-1963, undated (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 13-61)
    Zabriskie Gallery
    Zacharias, Jean
    Zaus, Earl A.
    Zegarelli, Dr.
    Zeltzerman, M.
    Zeirler, William S.
    Zierner, Thelma
    Zinn
    Zinsser, J. S.
    Zinsser, William H.
    Zion, A.
    Zipin, M.
    Zorach, William
    Zorne, Mrs. A. E.
    Zsissly
  - Zucker - Zunser, 1953-1968, undated (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 62-159)
    Zucker, Harry T./Zucker, Weiden and Shapiro
    R. M. Zucker and Company
    Zunser, Shomer
  - Unknown and Illegible, 1922-1968, undated (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 161-271)
  - Stenographer's Notebook (outgoing letters in shorthand), 1947-Jan. 31, 1948 (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 273-374)
- Financial Records, 1919-1968, undated, Series 2:; (Boxes 15-17; 2.6 linear feet; Reel 5869)
  Of particular interest are monthly insurance schedules indicating painting titles and values, and specifying additions and deletions from the previous month. The remaining insurance records have not been microfilmed.
  Investment records, filed by names of investment firms, relate to numerous personal and business accounts, including estates of Rehn family members.
  Miscellaneous financial records include a file relating to the estate of Frank Rehn's first wife, Peggy W. Rehn, and gallery inventories. Two volumes of receipts record incoming paintings; similar loose receipts are with Series 1. Paid bills are for routine business expenses and some personal expenses; the art-related purchases documented here are framing and painting conservation. Receipts for paintings bought by the gallery are with Series 1.
  This series is arranged into 6 subseries:
  2.1: Banking, 1920-1968
  2.2: Insurance, 1920-1968
  2.3: Investments, 1919-1968, undated
  2.4: Taxes, 1916-1964, undated
  2.5: Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1937-1951, undated
  2.6: Paid Bills, 1919-1969
  - Banking, 1920-1968, 2.1:
    - Bank for Savings (Margaret S. Rehn), 1929-1934 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Bank of New York (Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc.), 1967-1968 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Bankers Trust Company (John J. Clancy and J. J. Clancy Special), 1953-1963, (2 folders) (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Chase National Bank (Margaret S. Rehn), 1946-1947 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Chemical Bank and Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn), 1937 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - East River Savings Bank (John J. Clancy), 1959-1965 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Empire Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc.), 1933-1968, undated (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Empire Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn), 1919-1942 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Empire Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn Special), 1941-1953 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Empire Trust Company (Estate of Frank K. M. Rehn), 1964 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Empire Trust Company (Estate of Peggy W. Rehn), 1942-1952 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Manchester Trust Company, 1942-1948 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Loans (Frank K. M. Rehn and John J. Clancy), 1920-1966 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Safe Deposit Rental Receipts (Frank K. M. Rehn, Peggy W. Rehn, and John J. Clancy), 1919-1966 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
  - Insurance, 1920-1968, 2.2:
    - Insurance Policies, 1920-1968, (3 folders) (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Insurance Policies, 1923-1966 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Insurance Schedules, 1922-1966, (3 folders) (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 380-792)
  - Investments, 1919-1968, undated, 2.3:
    - H. L. Allen and Company, 1923 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Dreyfus Fund, Incorporated, 1968 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Hemphill, Noyes and Co./Hemphill, Noyes, Graham, Parsons and Co., 1942-1964, undated (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Jesup and Lamont, 1927 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Lee, Higginson and Company, 1922-1925, undated (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1919-1953, undated (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
  - Taxes, 1916-1964, undated, 2.4:
    - Federal, 1918-1949, 1963 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Payroll, 1950-1966 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - New York State, 1920-1964 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Gloucester, Mass., 1916-1954 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Englewood Cliffs, N. J., 1940-1955 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - New York, N. Y., 1919-1964 (Box 15, Reel unmicrofilmed)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1937-1951, undated, 2.5:
    - Estate of Peggy W. Rehn, 1942-1951 (Box 16, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Inventories of Gallery Stock (includes consignments and frames), circa 1919-1963, n.d (Box 16, Reel 5869, Frame 798-878)
    - Notes regarding Business Expenses and Income, 1919-1967, undated, (3 folders) (Box 16, Reel 5869, Frame 880-1185)
    - Receipts for Incoming Paintings, 1937-1939; 1946-1948, (2 vols.) (Box 16, Reel 5869, Frame 1189-1331)
  - Paid Bills, 1919-1969, 2.6:
    - A - Z, 1918-1950, (17 folders) (Box 16, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - A - Z, 1951-1968, (18 folders) (Box 17, Reel unmicrofilmed)
- Scrapbooks, 1919-1940, Series 3:; (Boxes 23-24; 0.6 linear feet; Reels 5869-5870)
  This series contains five volumes documenting the activities of Rehn Galleries and its associated artists, 1919, 1923-1941, that contain clippings and a small number of exhibition catalogs. An autographed photograph of Walter Griffin is in volume 1. Items on former reel NY59/17 (frames 165-293) were missing from volume 1 when inspected in October 1981. This material was thought to have been returned to the donor after microfilming, and reader-printer copies were inserted as substitutes in 1981. In 2003, these items were found and are now interfiled with the appropriate series (correspondence, printed matter, works of art, and miscellaneous items).
  - Vol. 1: 1919, 1923-1928 (Box 23 (sol), Reel 5869, Frame 1337-1421)
  - Vol. 2: 1928-1930 (Box 23 (sol), Reel 5869, Frame 1423-1696)
  - Vol. 3: 1930-1933 (Box 24 (sol), Reel 5870, Frame 13-132)
  - Vol. 4: 1934-1937 (Box 24 (sol), Reel 5870, Frame 134-201)
  - Vol. 5: 1937-1941 (Box 24 (sol), Reel 5870, Frame 203-261)
- Printed Matter, 1882-1969, undated, Series 4:; (Boxes 18-20; 2.5 linear feet; Reels 5870-5872)
  Printed matter relating to Rehn Galleries consists of items about the gallery, as well as publications produced by Rehn Galleries. Included are feature articles, exhibition reviews, announcements and catalogs of artists affiliated with the gallery. Also found here are exhibition catalogs, press releases, and invitations produced by the gallery. General, art-related printed matter consists of articles, auction catalogs, advertisements, and publications of various museums, arts organizations, and schools; also included are feature articles, exhibition reviews, announcements, and catalogs of artists not affiliated with Rehn Galleries. Additional printed items concern miscellaneous subjects that are not art-related.
  This series is arranged into 3 subseries:
  4.1: Rehn Galleries, 1919-1969, undated
  4.2: General, Art-Related, 1882-1968, undated
  4.3: Miscellaneous Subjects, Not Art-Related, 1910-1967, undated
  - Rehn Galleries, 1919-1969, undated, 4.1:
    - Rehn Galleries Advertisements, 1925-1968, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 266-299)
    - Rehn Artists, A - Z (17 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5870)
      - Bacon - Botkin, 1918-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 301-347)
      - Brook - Brown, 1940-1968, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 348-389)
      - Burchfield, Charles E., 1935-1961 (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 390-556)
      - Campanella - Fiene, 1930-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 557-608)
      - Gikow - Hite, 1921-1968, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 609-673)
      - Hopper, Edward, 1934-1967, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 674-756)
      - Hubbard - Kaufman, 1942-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 757-831)
      - Kimball - Kroll, 1932-1967, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 832-900)
      - Lathrop - Mangravite, 1920-1965, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 901-970)
      - Marsh, Reginald, 1934-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 971-1052)
      - Mattson - Powers, 1920-1967, undated (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 1053-1154)
      - Raffo - Schwieder, 1933-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 13-50)
      - Sparhawk-Jones - Spruance, 1932-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 51-94)
      - Strater, Henry, 1961-1968, undated (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 95-175)
      - Tomlin - Twachtman, 1921-1964, undated (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 176-231)
      - Watkins - Young, 1922-1963, undated (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 232-287)
    - Rehn Artists, Group Shows, 1920-1944, (3 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 289-532)
    - Rehn Artists, Group Shows, 1945-1968, undated, (7 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5871, Frame 535-1021)
    - Rehn Galleries Exhibition Catalogs, Press Releases, Invitations, 1920-1969, undated, (6 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5871, Frame 1023-1328)
    - Rehn Galleries Exhibition Catalogs, Press Releases, Invitations, cont., 1920-1969, undated, (6 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5872, Frame 13-51)
    - Rehn Galleries Exhibition Catalogs, Press Releases, Invitations, 1920-1966, undated, (3 folders; duplicates unfilmed) (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
  - General, Art-Related, 1882-1968, undated, 4.2:
    - Advertisements for Frames and Supplies, undated (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Articles about Art Collectors, 1928-1967, undated (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Articles about Art Sales and Prices, 1922-1963, undated (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Articles about Fakes and Forgeries, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Articles about Museums, 1949-1966 (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Articles about U.S. Exhibition in Moscow, 1959 (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Articles about Miscellaneous Topics, 1921-1965 (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Artists (not Rehn), A-K, 1919-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 19, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Artists (not Rehn), L - Z, 1920-1967, undated, (4 folders) (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Artists (not Rehn), Group Shows, 1931-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Auction Catalogs, 1882-1961, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Book Prospectuses and Information about Periodical Subscriptions and Advertising, 1921-1962, undated (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Fuller Building Floor Plan, undated (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Publications, Art Schools, 1933-1963 (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Publications, Arts Organizations, A - Z, 1953-1968, undated (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Publications, Museums, A - Z, 1936-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, Not Art-Related, 1910-1967, undated, 4.3:
    - Miscellaneous, 1910-1967, undated, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel unmicrofilmed)
- Miscellaneous Records, circa 1920-1968, undated, Series 5:; (Boxes 20-21; 0.7 linear feet; Reel 5872)
  Artwork consists of undated painted Christmas cards by Yeffee Kimball and Denny Winters, and a painted greeting card by Warren Chappell sent to Reginald Marsh. Pen and ink drawings, 1925-1927 and undated, are by George Luks, Reginald Marsh, Mahonri Young, and unidentified artists. Other artwork includes a sketchbook and watercolor painting by Reginald Marsh.
  Among the writings are a short story, "The Power of Money," probably by Frank K. M. Rehn, poems by Coleman Kamile and unknown, and an unsigned essay titled "An American Collector."
  - Artwork, A-Z, 1925-1927, undated, (3 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5872)
    - Chappell, Warren, undated (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 55-56)
    - Kimball, Yeffee, undated (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 57-58)
    - Luks, George, 1925 (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 59-60)
    - Marsh, Reginald, undated (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 61-70)
    - Winters, Denny, undated (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 71-73)
    - Young, Mahonri, undated (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 74-76)
    - Unidentified, 1926-1927, undated (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 77-85)
  - Lists of Paintings, circa 1920-1968, undated, (7 folders) (Box 21 (pam), Reel 5872, Frame 87-725)
  - Names, Addresses, and Telephone Numbers, circa 1920-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 21 (pam), Reel unmicrofilmed)
  - Notes about Artists, A - Z, 1940s, undated (Box 21 (pam), Reel 5872, Frame 729-807)
  - Notes about Paintings, undated (Box 21 (pam), Reel 5872, Frame 809-818)
  - Notes, Miscellaneous, 1919-1968, undated (Box 21 (pam), Reel 5872, Frame 820-914)
  - Painting Labels, undated (Box 21 (pam), Reel 5872, Frame 916-918)
  - Writings, undated (Box 21 (pam), Reel 5872, Frame 920-934)
- Photographs, 1871-1966, undated, Series 6:; (Boxes 22, 24, and OV 25; 1.0 linear feet; Reel 5872)
  Photographs of people include both artists represented by Rehn Galleries and several not affiliated with the gallery. A 1945 group portrait of gallery artists includes Alexander Brook, Charles Burchfield, John Carroll, John Clancy, Edward Hopper, Morris Kantor, Peppino Mangravite, Reginald Marsh, Henry Mattson, George Picken, Henry Varnum Poor, Frank K. M. Rehn, Eugene Speicher, Bradley Walker Tomlin, and Franklin C. Watkins. Another group portrait is of the 27th Carnegie International Jury of Award and American Committee of Selection. Noticeably absent are likenesses of Frank K. M. Rehn and John C. Clancy. Photographs of works of art are by Rehn Galleries' artists and others.
  Reginald Marsh's photographs consist of family and personal photographs that were either given to Rehn Galleries or perhaps borrowed for research at the time of his memorial exhibition. Views of Marsh from early childhood through old age consist of studio portraits, informal photographs, and publicity shots of Marsh at work; also included are photographs of family and friends, and a small family album, with few individuals identified. Other photographs are of Marsh's childhood drawings executed between ages 4 and 8, and buildings, including two identified as mother's church and father's church.
  Miscellaneous subjects are a dog and exhibitions. Exhibition installation views consist of an unidentified exhibition, circa 1923, probably Rehn Galleries, probably at 5 West 50th Street, and two views of the "Rehn Group," possibly at the Carnegie Institute, 1920.
  This series is arranged into 4 subseries:
  6.1: People, 1917-1966, undated
  6.2: Works of Art, circa 1905, 1960-1964, undated
  6.3: Reginald Marsh's Photographs, 1871-1952, undated
  6.4: Miscellaneous Subjects, circa 1923, 1928, 1950, undated
  - People, 1917-1966, undated, 6.1:
    - Ames, A., undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 939-940)
    - Carroll, John and Pinky, circa 1935 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 942-943)
    - Edelstein, Babette, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 944-945)
    - Hartman, Rosella, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 947)
    - Hopper, Edward, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 949-950)
    - Marsh, Reginald (See 6.3: Reginald Marsh's Photographs) (Box 22, Reel 5872)
    - Mattson, Henry, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 952-953)
    - Meyer, Herbert (See 6.3: Reginald Marsh's Photographs) (Box 22, Reel 5872)
    - Mintz, Raymond (?), 1960 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 955-956)
    - Little, Dr. Charles S. (See Roosevelt, Gov. Franklin D. and Dr. Charles S. Little) (Box 22, Reel 5872)
    - Rehn, Margarete, 1966 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 958-959)
    - Roosevelt, Governor Franklin D. and Dr. Charles S. Little (at Letchworth Village, Thiells, N. Y.), 1931 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 961-966)
    - Rosen, Charles, 1925 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 968)
    - Wilder, Ruth, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 970-971)
    - Unknown (includes "Spike")1917, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 973-976)
    - Artists of the Rehn Galleries (Peter A. Juley and Son, Photographers), 1945, (Items also scanned on Reel 1817, frames 1329-1330) (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 978-979)
    - 27th Carnegie International Exhibition, Jury of Award and American Committee of Selection, 1928, (Oversized item housed in Box 24) (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 981)
  - Works of Art, circa 1905, 1960-1964, undated, 6.2:
    - Bellows, George, circa 1905, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 984-987)
    - Blagden, Allen, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 989)
    - Brook, Alexander, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Brown, Gwyneth King (See King, Gwyneth) (Box 22, Reel 5872)
    - Burchfield, Charles E. (includes family collection of Mr. and Mrs. Walter Fillin, Rockville Centre, NY), undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 992-994)
    - Busch, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 996)
    - Chapin, James, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 998-1002)
    - Corbino, Jon, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Crane, Bruce, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1006-1007)
    - Crespi, Danielle, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1009-1010)
    - Dasburg, Andrew, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1012-1019)
    - Driggs, Elsie, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1021-1022)
    - Edelstein, Babette, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1024-1031)
    - Fromentin, Eugene, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1033-1034)